Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Administrative Assistant Files, 1962-2010; I.
  - David Brog, 1993-2004; 5.
    - Same-sex marriage, 2003-2004 (Box 591, Folder 21)
    - Saudi Arabian Accountability Bill, 2003-2004 (Box 591, Folder 22)
    - See-me's, 2003-2004 (Box 592, Folder 1)
    - Senatorial advice, 1996-1997 (Box 592, Folder 2)
    - Siemens, 2004 (Box 592, Folder 3)
    - Small businesses, 2004 (Box 592, Folder 4)
    - Social Security and retirement age, 1998 (Box 592, Folder 5)
    - Summer Session runners, 1999 (Box 592, Folder 6)
    - Supreme Court decisions, 1994-2003 (Box 592, Folder 7)
    - Supreme Court panel, 1996-1998 (Box 592, Folder 8-9)
    - Supreme Court panel event, 2003-2004 (Box 592, Folder 10)
    - Term limits, 1994-1995 (Box 592, Folder 11)
    - Terrorism, 2003-2004 (Box 592, Folder 12)
    - Terrorism op-ed, 2003 (Box 592, Folder 13)
    - Title III, 2004 (Box 592, Folder 14)
    - Trade treaties, 2003 (Box 592, Folder 15)
    - Travel notes, 2001 (Box 592, Folder 16)
    - Verizon tax bill, 2001-2003 (Box 592, Folder 17)
    - Victims' rights, 2003 (Box 592, Folder 18)
    - VIP mail, 1998 (Box 592, Folder 19)
    - VIP mail, 2002-2004 (Box 592, Folder 20)
    - Vouchers, 2002-2003 (Box 592, Folder 21)
    - Workplace Religious Freedom Act, 2003 (Box 592, Folder 22)
    - WorldCom, 2003 (Box 592, Folder 23-24)
    - Youth development block grants, 1995-1996 (Box 592, Folder 25)
  - Joanne Brown, 1982-1985; 6.
    Joanne Brown served as secretary, 1984-1988.
    - Chronological file, September 1982 (Box 592, Folder 26)
    - Chronological file, October 1982 (Box 592, Folder 27)
    - Chronological file, November 1982 (Box 592, Folder 28)
    - Chronological file, December 1982 (Box 592, Folder 29)
    - Chronological file, January 1983 (Box 593, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file, February 1983 (Box 593, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file, March 1983 (Box 593, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file, April 1983 (Box 593, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file, May 1983 (Box 593, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file, June 1983 (Box 593, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file, July 1983 (Box 593, Folder 7)
    - Chronological file, August 1983 (Box 593, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file, September 1983 (Box 593, Folder 9)
    - Chronological file, October 1983 (Box 593, Folder 10)
    - Chronological file, November 1983 (Box 593, Folder 11)
    - Chronological file, December 1983 (Box 593, Folder 12)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, March 1984 (Box 593, Folder 13)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, June 1984 (Box 593, Folder 14)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, July 1984 (Box 594, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, August 1984 (Box 594, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, September 1984 (Box 594, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, October 1984 (Box 594, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, November 1984 (Box 594, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, November 1984 (Box 594, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, December 1984 (Box 594, Folder 7)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, December 1984 (Box 594, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, January 1985 (Box 594, Folder 9)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, January 1985 (Box 594, Folder 10)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, January 1985 (Box 594, Folder 11)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, February 1985 (Box 594, Folder 12)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, February 1985 (Box 594, Folder 13)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, February 1985 (Box 594, Folder 14)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, March 1985 (Box 594, Folder 15)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, March 1985 (Box 594, Folder 16)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, March 1985 (Box 594, Folder 17)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, April 1985 (Box 594, Folder 18)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, April 1985 (Box 594, Folder 19)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, April 1985 (Box 594, Folder 20)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, May 1985 (Box 594, Folder 21)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, May 1985 (Box 594, Folder 22)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, May 1985 (Box 594, Folder 23)
    - Chronological file, Paul Michel signed, June 1985 (Box 594, Folder 24)
    - Chronological file, AS dictated, June 1985 (Box 594, Folder 25)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, June 1985 (Box 594, Folder 26)
    - Chronological file, AS signed, July 1985 (Box 594, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence Log, January-December 1984 (Box 594, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence Log, November-December 1984 (Box 594, Folder 29)
  - Bill Cahill, 2004; 7.
    Bill Cahill served as chief counsel for veterans' affairs, 2004.
    - Veterans' Affairs, 2004 (Box 594, Folder 30)
  - Barry Caldwell, 1992-1996; 8.
    Barry Caldwell served as: counsel, 1991-1992; and chief of staff, 1993-1996.
    - Campaign travel, 1996 (Box 594, Folder 31)
    - Citizens for Arlen Specter expenses, 1994 (Box 594, Folder 32-33)
    - Congressional Accountability Act, 1996 (Box 594, Folder 34)
    - "The Day After" Study, 1993 (Box 594, Folder 35)
    - "The Day After" Study, 1993 (Box 595, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising, 1996 (Box 595, Folder 2)
    - Gift rule, 1996 (Box 595, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary Committee initiatives, 1992 (Box 595, Folder 4)
    - Mail operations, 1996 (Box 595, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 1994-1996 (Box 595, Folder 6)
    - Personal use of campaign funds, 1996 (Box 595, Folder 7)
    - Staff political activity, 1994 (Box 595, Folder 8)
    - Town meeting notices, 1995-1996 (Box 595, Folder 9)
  - Stan Caldwell, 1981-2010; 9.
    Stan Caldwell served as: field representative, Pittsburgh office, 1998-1999; community affairs coordinator, Pittsburgh office, 2003-2005; and executive director, Pittsburgh office, 2007-2010.
    - Chronological indexes, 1981-1982 (Box 595, Folder 10)
    - Chronological indexes, 1981-1996 (Box 595, Folder 11)
    - Chronological indexes, County visits and open houses, 1981-1996 (Box 595, Folder 12)
    - Chronological indexes, Specter visits, 1981-1990 (Box 595, Folder 13)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania summary, 1981-2010 (Box 595, Folder 14)
    - Trip files, July-August 2006 (Box 595, Folder 15)
    - Trip files, September-October 2006 (Box 595, Folder 16)
    - Trip files, January-June 2007 (Box 595, Folder 17)
    - Trip files, July-August 2007 (Box 595, Folder 18)
    - Trip files, October-November 2007 (Box 595, Folder 19)
    - Trip files, January-March 2008 (Box 595, Folder 20)
    - Trip files, April-August 2008 (Box 595, Folder 21)
    - Trip files, October 2008-April 2009 (Box 595, Folder 22)
    - Trip files, June-August 2009 (Box 595, Folder 23)
    - Trip files, September-November 2009 (Box 596, Folder 1)
    - Trip files, January-March 2010 (Box 596, Folder 2)
    - Trip files, April-May 2010 (Box 596, Folder 3)
    - Trip files, June-September 2010 (Box 596, Folder 4)
    - Western Pennsylvania, Index, 1983-1985 (Box 596, Folder 5)
    - Western Pennsylvania, Index, 1986-1997 (Box 596, Folder 6)
    - Western Pennsylvania, Visits, 1997-1998 (Box 596, Folder 7)
    - Western Pennsylvania, Visits, 1999-2004 (Box 596, Folder 8)
    - Western Pennsylvania, Visits, 2005-2010 (Box 596, Folder 9)
  - Tamika Carson, 2005; 10.
    Tamika Carson served as special projects director/intern coordinator, 2004-2005.
    - Emails, 2005 (Box 596, Folder 10)
  - Allison Cricks, 1983-2001; 11.
    Allison Cricks served as staff assistant, 2000-2001; asisstant to the chief of staff, 2001-2002; and scheduler, 2003-2004.
    - Accepted invitations, June 1988 (Box 596, Folder 11)
    - Accepted invitations, July 1988 (Box 596, Folder 12)
    - Accepted invitations, August 1988 (Box 596, Folder 13)
    - Appointment requests, 1987-1988 (Box 596, Folder 14)
    - Building plans (Box 596, Folder 15)
    - Citizens for Arlen Specter (CAS), Correspondence, 1988 (Box 596, Folder 16)
    - CAS, Event, 1983 (Box 596, Folder 17)
    - CAS, Event, 1987 (Box 596, Folder 18)
    - CAS, Event, 1990 (Box 597, Folder 1)
    - CAS, Invitations, 1986-1991 (Box 597, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Medal of Honor (CMH), 1995 (Box 597, Folder 3)
    - CMH, Afternoon schedule, 1995 (Box 597, Folder 4)
    - CMH, Charitable organization filing, 1995 (Box 597, Folder 5)
    - CMH, Schedule and notes, 1995 (Box 597, Folder 6)
    - Eisenhower Fellowship, 1998 (Box 597, Folder 7)
    - Ethics Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 597, Folder 8)
    - Letters, 1999-2001 (Box 597, Folder 9)
    - Long range schedules, 1986 (Box 597, Folder 10)
    - Memos, 1999-2001 (Box 597, Folder 11)
    - Memos, From Cricks, 1987 (Box 597, Folder 12)
    - Personal, Family, 1996-2001 (Box 597, Folder 13)
    - Personal, Squash, Bible study, Reunion, 2000 (Box 597, Folder 14)
    - Room reservations, 1987-1988 (Box 597, Folder 15)
    - Sample letters, 1996-1998 (Box 597, Folder 16)
    - Schedules, 1980s-1990s (Box 597, Folder 17)
    - Student appointment requests, 1988 (Box 597, Folder 18)
    - Trip files, Sun Valley, 1987 (Box 597, Folder 19)
    - Trip files, CODEL, 1998 (Box 597, Folder 20-21)
    - Trip files, CODEL, 1999 (Box 597, Folder 22)
    - Trip files, Cuba, 1999 (Box 597, Folder 23)
    - Trip files, January 2000 (Box 597, Folder 24)
    - Trip files, CODEL, 2000 (Box 597, Folder 25)
  - Daniel Eaton, 1975-1989; 12.
    Daniel Eaton served as staff assistant, 1984-1986.
    - Accomplishments, 1986 (Box 598, Folder 1)
    - Anti-labor, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 2)
    - Bradford Regional Airport, 1984 (Box 598, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Research Services (CRS) health education programs, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 5)
    - Future of children's television, 1984 (Box 598, Folder 6)
    - Government affairs, 1986 (Box 598, Folder 7)
    - Hazleton, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 8)
    - Home equity background, 1986 (Box 598, Folder 9)
    - Informational copies from Wagner (Box 598, Folder 10-11)
    - Interstates, 1984 (Box 598, Folder 12)
    - Labor, 1982-1986 (Box 598, Folder 13)
    - Labor, VIP mail, 1986 (Box 598, Folder 14)
    - Legislative, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 15)
    - Letters, 1984 (Box 598, Folder 16)
    - Letters, Airco, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 17)
    - Letters, Bikini Atoll radiation, 1984-1985 (Box 598, Folder 18)
    - Letters, Chaplaincy Balance Act, 1984-1986 (Box 598, Folder 19)
    - Letters, Chester County, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 20)
    - Letters, Dear Colleagues, 1983-1985 (Box 598, Folder 21)
    - Letters, Drafts completed, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 22)
    - Letters, Education, 1984-1985 (Box 598, Folder 23-24)
    - Letters, Financial aid cuts, 1985 (Box 598, Folder 25)
    - Letters, Support for Specter, 1986-1987 (Box 598, Folder 26)
    - Letters, Transportation, 1985-1986 (Box 598, Folder 27)
    - Mailings and memos, 1984-1986 (Box 598, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 1)
    - Missed votes, 1975-1985 (Box 599, Folder 2)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees (Box 599, Folder 3)
    - Newsclips, 1985-1986 (Box 599, Folder 4)
    - Newsclips, Anti-handicapped education, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 5)
    - Newsclips, Beyond Relief newsletter, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 6)
    - Newsclips, Budget, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 7)
    - Newsclips, Delaware River Port Authority, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 8)
    - Newsclips, South Africa/divestment, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 9)
    - Newsclips, Student aid cuts, 1984-1985 (Box 599, Folder 10)
    - Newsclips, Transportation, 1984-1985 (Box 599, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 12)
    - Opposition, Newsclips, 1985-1986 (Box 599, Folder 13)
    - Opposition, Research, 1984-1986 (Box 599, Folder 14)
    - Opposition, Votes, 1980-1986 (Box 599, Folder 15)
    - Organ procurement, 1983-1985 (Box 599, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania College of Optometry, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 17)
    - Post office, 1981 (Box 599, Folder 18)
    - Publications, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 19)
    - Senate Youth Programs, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 21)
    - Veterans, 1985 (Box 599, Folder 22)
    - Veterans, Agency press releases, 1986-1989 (Box 599, Folder 23)
    - Veterans, Current cases, 1986 (Box 599, Folder 24)
    - Veterans, Dear Colleagues, 1985-1986 (Box 599, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, Memos and talking points, 1986 (Box 599, Folder 26)
    - Veterans, National Association of State Veterans Homes, 1986 (Box 599, Folder 27)
    - Veterans, News clippings and newsletters, 1986 (Box 599, Folder 28)
    - Veterans, Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD), 1980-1984 (Box 599, Folder 29)
    - Veterans, Voting records, 1984 (Box 599, Folder 30)
  - Kathy Groetzinger, 1981-1982; 13.
    Kathy Groetzinger in Senator Specter's office, with materials dated 1981-1982.
    - Block grants, 1981 (Box 599, Folder 31)
    - Boy Scout letters, 1981 (Box 599, Folder 32)
    - Brith Shalom House, 1981 (Box 599, Folder 33)
    - Bucks County, 1982 (Box 599, Folder 34)
    - Citizans Utility Board, 1982 (Box 599, Folder 35)
    - Complaint file, 1982 (Box 599, Folder 36)
    - Cordomatic, 1982 (Box 599, Folder 37)
    - Dechert distribution, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 1)
    - Documents recieved from Washington, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 2)
    - Fishtown Civic Association, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 3)
    - Future file, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Hospital, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 5)
    - Hunting and fishing, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 7)
    - Letters, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 8)
    - Materials sent to Bruce, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 9)
    - Materials sent to Dan, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 10)
    - Materials sent to Gordon, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 11)
    - Materials sent to June, 1981 (Box 600, Folder 12)
    - Materials sent to Sheila, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 13)
    - Materials sent to Sylvia, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 14)
    - Monthly reports, February 1982 (Box 600, Folder 15)
    - National Rifle Association, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 16)
    - Nuclear Disarmament Open Forum, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia press releases, 1981 (Box 600, Folder 18)
    - Radio editorials, 1981 (Box 600, Folder 19)
    - Reports, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 20)
    - Robbins Avenue closing, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 21)
    - Schedules, 1981-1982 (Box 600, Folder 22)
    - Staff travel, 1981 (Box 600, Folder 23)
    - Weekly mail reports, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 24)
    - Wilkes-Barre file, 1982 (Box 600, Folder 25)
  - Peter Grollman, 1997-2000; 14.
    Peter Grollman served as: assistant to the chief of staff, 1998; special projects director, 1999; legislative aide, 2000; legislative assistant, 2001-2002.
    - American Iron and Steel Institute, 1999 (Box 600, Folder 26)
    - Antidumping, 1997-2000 (Box 600, Folder 27-28)
    - Chronological file, May 1998 (Box 600, Folder 29)
    - Chronological file, June 1998 (Box 600, Folder 30)
    - Chronological file, July 1998 (Box 600, Folder 31)
    - Chronological file, August 1998 (Box 600, Folder 32)
    - Chronological file, September 1998 (Box 600, Folder 33-34)
    - Chronological file, October 1998 (Box 600, Folder 35-36)
    - Chronological file, February 1999 (Box 601, Folder 1)
    - Bob LaRussa, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 2)
    - Memos, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh field hearing, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 4)
    - Postal service, 1998 (Box 601, Folder 5)
    - Save America's Treasures, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 6)
    - Steel, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 7)
    - Steel appropriations, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 8)
    - Steel, briefings, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 9)
    - Steel crisis, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 10)
    - Steel hearings, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 11)
    - Steel loan fund, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 12)
    - Tin products, 2000 (Box 601, Folder 13)
    - Unfair Foreign Competition Act, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 14-15)
    - Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corporation, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 16)
    - White House steel initiative, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 17)
    - Wire rod industry, 1999 (Box 601, Folder 18)
  - Glenn Groninger, 1993-1995; 15.
    Glenn Groninger served as executive assistant, 1994-1996.
    - Constituent requests, September 1993 (Box 601, Folder 19)
    - Constituent requests, October 1993 (Box 601, Folder 20)
    - Constituent requests, November 1993 (Box 601, Folder 21)
    - Constituent requests, December 1993 (Box 601, Folder 22)
    - Constituent requests, January 1994 (Box 602, Folder 1)
    - Constituent requests, February 1994 (Box 602, Folder 2)
    - Constituent requests, March 1994 (Box 602, Folder 3)
    - Constituent requests, April 1994 (Box 602, Folder 4)
    - Constituent requests, May 1994 (Box 602, Folder 5)
    - Constituent requests, June 1994 (Box 602, Folder 6)
    - Constituent requests, July 1994 (Box 602, Folder 7)
    - Constituent requests, August 1994 (Box 602, Folder 8)
    - Constituent requests, September 1994 (Box 602, Folder 9)
    - Constituent requests, October 1994 (Box 602, Folder 10)
    - Constituent requests, November 1994 (Box 602, Folder 11)
    - Constituent requests, December 1994 (Box 602, Folder 12)
    - Constituent requests, February 1995 (Box 602, Folder 13)
    - Constituent requests, March 1995 (Box 602, Folder 14)
    - Constituent requests, April 1995 (Box 602, Folder 15)
    - Constituent requests, May 1995 (Box 602, Folder 16)
    - Constituent requests, June 1995 (Box 602, Folder 17)
    - Constituent requests, July 1995 (Box 602, Folder 18)
    - Constituent requests, August 1995 (Box 602, Folder 19)
    - Constituent requests, September 1995 (Box 602, Folder 20)
    - Constituent requests, October 1995 (Box 602, Folder 21)
    - Constituent requests, November 1995 (Box 602, Folder 22)
    - Constituent requests, December 1995 (Box 602, Folder 23)
  - Mark Heilbrun, 2002-2010; 16.
    Mark Heilbrun served as senior counsel, 2002-2005.
    - AEGIS, 2004 (Box 602, Folder 24)
    - Maureen Faulkner, 2004 (Box 602, Folder 25)
    - First responders, 2003 (Box 602, Folder 26)
    - First responders, Butler, 2003-2004 (Box 602, Folder 27)
    - First responders, Chester, 2004 (Box 602, Folder 28)
    - First responders, Emergency, 2002-2003 (Box 602, Folder 29)
    - First responders, Erie, 2004 (Box 602, Folder 30)
    - First responders, Firefighters Grant Program, 2003 (Box 602, Folder 31)
    - First responders, Greene, 2004 (Box 602, Folder 32)
    - First responders, Indiana, 2003 (Box 602, Folder 33)
    - First responders, KME Fire Apparatus, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 1)
    - First responders, Newsclips, 2003 (Box 603, Folder 2)
    - First responders, Pennsylvania initiatives, 2003 (Box 603, Folder 3)
    - First responders, Pennsylvania Professional Fire Chiefs Association, 2003-2004 (Box 603, Folder 4)
    - First responders, Pittsburgh interoperability, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 5)
    - First responders, RAND Corp. Center for Terrorism Risk Management Policy, 2005 (Box 603, Folder 6)
    - First responders, Regional task forces, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 7)
    - First responders, St. Joseph's University, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 8)
    - First responders, State troopers, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 9)
    - Insurance Articles of Incorporation, 2002-2003 (Box 603, Folder 10)
    - Iraq, 2003 (Box 603, Folder 11)
    - Judiciary, 2005 (Box 603, Folder 12)
    - Letters, 2003-2004 (Box 603, Folder 13)
    - Letters, Rosenstock (Box 603, Folder 14)
    - Letters, Wecht, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 15)
    - Nomination panel, 2002-2003 (Box 603, Folder 16)
    - Notes, July-August 2003 (Box 603, Folder 17)
    - Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 603, Folder 18)
    - Notes, May 2004 (Box 603, Folder 19)
    - Notes, November 2004 (Box 603, Folder 20)
    - Notes (Box 603, Folder 21)
    - Notes, Public health initiative, 2005-2010 (Box 603, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Coal Association, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 23)
    - Private relief Duisberg, 2001 (Box 603, Folder 24)
    - Schedules, 2002-2003 (Box 603, Folder 25)
    - Senate hearing, Thrift savings, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 26)
    - Senate hearing, S.346, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 27)
    - Senate hearing, Section 529, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 28)
    - Senate training, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 29)
    - SNCF lawsuit, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 30)
    - Jerry Sorkin, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 31)
    - Travel and receipts, 2004 (Box 603, Folder 32)
  - Mark Klugheit, 1973-1995; 17.
    Mark Klugheit served as general counsel, 1994-1996.
    - Robert Bork, 1987 (Box 603, Folder 33)
    - Campaign contributions, Background information, 1985-1992 (Box 603, Folder 34)
    - Campaign contributions, Documents and notes, 1992-1993 (Box 603, Folder 35)
    - Campaign contributions, Victory Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 603, Folder 36)
    - Campaign contributions, Marshall Williams, 1992 (Box 603, Folder 37)
    - Cases, 1973-1978 (Box 603, Folder 38)
    - CAS stationery, 1992 (Box 603, Folder 39)
    - Civil rights, 1990 (Box 604, Folder 1-2)
    - Constituent mail, 1992-1995 (Box 604, Folder 3)
    - Ethics, 1993-1994 (Box 604, Folder 4)
    - Evidence notes, undated (Box 604, Folder 5)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, American Law Division memo, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 6)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Biographical and third-party materials, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 7)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Decisions and articles, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 8)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, First amendment, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 9)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Hearings, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 10)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Newsclips, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 11)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Senate Judiciary Committee initial questionnaire, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 12)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg nomination, Specter inquiry and questioning, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 13)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Background information, 1989 (Box 604, Folder 14)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Case text and Congressional Record, 1989 (Box 604, Folder 15)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Drafts for paper, undated (Box 604, Folder 16)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Memos, 1989 (Box 604, Folder 17-18)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Notes, 1989 (Box 604, Folder 19)
    - William Hastings impeachment, Senate statements, 1989 (Box 604, Folder 20)
    - Hertling documents, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 21)
    - Line-item veto, 1993-1994 (Box 605, Folder 1)
    - Joseph McDade, Michael Baylson, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 2)
    - Joseph McDade, Case text, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 3)
    - Joseph McDade, Philadelphia Inquirer, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 4)
    - Joseph McDade, Subpoena background and notes, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 5)
    - Joseph McDade, Subpoena documents, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 6)
    - Joseph McDade, Subpoena as filed in U.S. District Court, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 7)
    - Joseph McDade, Tax information, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 8)
    - Medical malpractice, 1994 (Box 605, Folder 9)
    - Memos, 1994 (Box 605, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 605, Folder 11)
    - Nominations, 1994-1995 (Box 605, Folder 12)
    - Supreme Court nominations, 1987-1992 (Box 605, Folder 13)
    - Lynn Yeakel, 1992 (Box 605, Folder 14)
  - Larry Kosten, 1981-2002; 18.
    Larry Kosten served as staff attorney, 2002-2003.
    - Campaign finance hearings, 2000 (Box 605, Folder 15)
    - Campaign finance investigation, 2000 (Box 605, Folder 16)
    - DOJ oversight hearings, 2001 (Box 605, Folder 17)
    - Department of Treasury class action suits, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 18)
    - FBI, Meeting, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 19)
    - FBI, Reorganization, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 20)
    - Federal Judicial Nomination Resolution, undated (Box 605, Folder 21)
    - First amendment rights of aliens, 2001 (Box 605, Folder 22)